<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Octavian Hasna</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/</link><description>Recent content on Octavian Hasna</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hasna.ro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DexOffline</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/dexoffline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/dexoffline/</guid><description>Overview These applications help you find words in DEX (the Romanian language dictionary) without being online. Search words can be saved in history. Besides, you can check if a word is in the official Scrabble word list for Romanian language, you can read the feed with words of the day, generate valid words for the Scrabble game, play word games and much more.
Features DexOffline DexOffline Plus Search words in the local dictionary (DEX 2009) ✔ ✔ Search words online (dexonline.</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Last Updated: May 25, 2021
This privacy policy describes how Octavian Hasna (&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo;) and 3rd parties services (both &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) collect, use and share personal information of consumer users of the website (&amp;ldquo;site&amp;rdquo;) and of the following apps (&amp;ldquo;products&amp;rdquo;):
DexOffline for Windows DexOffline Plus for Windows DexOffline for Android DexOffline Plus for Android DexOffline for iOS DexOffline Plus for iOS What we collect We get information about you in a range of ways.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://www.hasna.ro/projects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hasna.ro/projects/</guid><description>DexOffline for Windows and for Android The goal of this app (desktop and mobile) is to find words in DEX (the Romanian language dictionary), generate Scrabble words, read word of day feed etc. More details
Time-series math The goal of this library is to provide optimised algorithms for time-series analysis and signal processing. https://github.com/octavian-h/time-series-math
Commons Weka The goal of this utility is to provide optimised functions to run validation tasks using Weka library.</description></item></channel></rss>